uccu.com 2006-11-14

# Utah Community Credit Union - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

As a member of Utah Community Credit Union, you do not have to worry about the security and confidentiality of your personal information. Utah Community Credit Union is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our members and the personal information shared with us in the course of doing business. The following privacy notice describes the privacy policy and practices followed by Utah Community Credit Union. It defines how we use and safeguard the members’ personal information. It also complies with privacy regulations and other applicable law. 

Information We Collect 

We collect nonpublic information about you from some or all of the following sources 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income.
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions and credit card usage.
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history.

Information We Disclose 

We may disclose all of the information we collect as described above to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We may also disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted by law. 

Our Security Measures 

We restrict access to nonpublic information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

You may receive a copy of the Utah Community Credit Union’s complete Privacy Notice by contacting us directly and requesting a copy be sent or given to you. 

Utah Community Credit Union  
188 West River Park Drive  
Provo, Utah 84604  
(801)-223-8188  
(800)-453-8188  

This notice meets the notification requirements of the National Credit Union Administration regulation on privacy of consumer information, Part 716.
